{
  "questions": [
    {
      "qid": 33,
      "question": "A motor pump-set of efficiency 80 % lifts 6000 litres of water per minute from a well 20 meters deep. If g=10 m/s2 then its input power is",
      "optiona": "20 kW",
      "optionb": "25 kW",
      "optionc": "16 kW",
      "optiond": "250 kW",
      "answer": "b",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 32,
      "question": "An electric pump draws water from a well of depth 50m at a rate of 2m^3 per second. The water is ejected from the pump with velocity, v=10m/s. If the efficiency of the pump Î·=80%, the input power consumption of the pump is: (g=10m/s^2)",
      "optiona": "1100 kW",
      "optionb": "880 kW",
      "optionc": "1375 kW",
      "optiond": "1080 kW",
      "answer": "c",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 31,
      "question": "A motor pump lifts 6 tons of water from a well of depth 2m to the first floor of height 35m from the ground floor in 20 minutes. The power of the pump (in kW) is \n[g = 10m/s^2]\n",
      "optiona": "6",
      "optionb": "1.85",
      "optionc": "12",
      "optiond": "3",
      "answer": "b",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 30,
      "question": " Kinetic energy of a body is increased most by doubling its",
      "optiona": "mass",
      "optionb": "density",
      "optionc": "weight",
      "optiond": "speed",
      "answer": "d",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 29,
      "question": "KE of a body increased by 44%. What is the percentage increase in the momentum?",
      "optiona": "10%",
      "optionb": "20%",
      "optionc": "33%",
      "optiond": "44%",
      "answer": "b",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 28,
      "question": "If K.E of a body increases by 0.1 %, the percentage increase in its momentum will be",
      "optiona": "0.05%",
      "optionb": "0.1%",
      "optionc": "1%",
      "optiond": "10%",
      "answer": "a",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 27,
      "question": "If the linear momentum is increased by 5%, the kinetic energy will increase by",
      "optiona": "50%",
      "optionb": "100%",
      "optionc": "150%",
      "optiond": "10%",
      "answer": "d",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 26,
      "question": "If momentum is increased by 20%, then kinetic energy increases by",
      "optiona": "48%",
      "optionb": "44%",
      "optionc": "40%",
      "optiond": "36%",
      "answer": "b",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 25,
      "question": "If the momentum of a body increases by 0.01%, its kinetic energy will increase by",
      "optiona": "0.01%",
      "optionb": "0.02%",
      "optionc": "0.04%",
      "optiond": "0.08%",
      "answer": "b",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    },
    {
      "qid": 24,
      "question": "If the increase in the kinetic energy of a body is 22 %, then the increase in the momentum will be",
      "optiona": "22%",
      "optionb": "44%",
      "optionc": "10%",
      "optiond": "30%",
      "answer": "c",
      "subject": "Physics",
      "marks": 1,
      "duration": 50
    }
  ],
  "total": 26
}